const questions = [
    {
        question: "Where did I use my first pick up line?",
        options: [
            "Are you a tissue? Cuz I can use you and throw away",
            "Are you a library book? Cuz I'm checking you out!",
            "Are you a 9 out of 10? Cuz I'm the one you need",
            "Spiders are great at weaving webs but suck at giving replies"
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What was our 0.5 date?",
        options: [
            "AM/PM",
            "Oriental fusion",
            "Paras Walk",
            "Select city walk"
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What was the reason I gave you to hold your hand for the first time?",
        options: [
            "I was scared of the dogs",
            "I can do palm reading",
            "I can listen to your heartbeat through your veins",
            "Comparing hand sizes"
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "When is our anniversary?",
        options: [
            "27 Sep",
            "21 Jun",
            "23 Jul",
            "25 Dec"
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which date changed the course of our relationship?",
        options: [
            "24 Dec",
            "20 Jun",
            "23 Aug",
            "21 Dec"
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is our go-to place to eat?",
        options: [
            "Taco Bell",
            "Tiny Tuscan",
            "KFC",
            "Chillis"
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What do we say when we do the same thing?",
        options: [
            "Twin",
            "Same same but different",
            "Déjà vu",
            "Mirror"
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How did I describe my personality when I met your family?",
        options: [
            "Like a lion",
            "Like a mirror",
            "Like a dog",
            "Like a beer"
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is our code word for SVC?",
        options: [
            "Session",
            "Fan",
            "Acting",
            "Hockey"
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Which Ananya is #1 on my list?",
        options: [
            "Zombie Ananya",
            "Eating Ananya",
            "Sleepy Ananya",
            "Hangry Ananya"
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which Ananya is last on my list?",
        options: [
            "Self-hater Ananya",
            "Drunk Ananya",
            "Unclean Ananya",
            "Stressed Ananya"
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "When did we drink together for the first time?",
        options: [
            "Our first anniversary",
            "When we watched Interstellar",
            "Our second anniversary",
            "Christmas Party"
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "If I had a penny for every time you slept on me after drinking, how many pennies would I have?",
        options: [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3"
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What was our position when you said 'I love you' to me?",
        options: [
            "69",
            "=",
            "||",
            "()"
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of distance is our relationship?",
        options: [
            "Online",
            "Short distance",
            "Medium distance",
            "Long distance"
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What book do I have 2 copies of?",
        options: [
            "Tintin",
            "Nightwing",
            "Batman",
            "Sentry"
        ],
        correct: 3
    }
];

window.questions = questions;